[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This card game is played by four players one of which is a dummy.", "correct_answer": "Bridge", "incorrect_answers": ["Rummy", "Hearts", "Spades"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happened to Madonna during the filming of the 1996 movie Evita?", "correct_answer": "She got pregnant.", "incorrect_answers": ["She broke her leg.", "She was infected with measles.", "Her father passed away."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first American novelist  to be considered an imoportant writer by the Europeans?", "correct_answer": "John Quincy Adams", "incorrect_answers": ["Washinton Irving", "James Fennimore Cooper", "Thomas  Howell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1999 horror movie is this quote from: We walked for 15 hours today, we ended up in the same place! Theres no one here to help you, THATS your motivation! THATS YOUR MOTIVATION!?", "correct_answer": "The Blair Witch Project", "incorrect_answers": ["Dead Alive", "The Hills Have Eyes", "I Know What You Did Last Summer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following statements about the Deoxyribonucleic acid (DNA), the molecule of heredity, is correct?", "correct_answer": "Its molecule is a double helix", "incorrect_answers": ["Its molecule is a single-stranded", "It encodes information from RNA", "It carries information to the Ribonucleic acid (RNA)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the British ruler at the time of the American Revolution?", "correct_answer": "George III", "incorrect_answers": ["Henry VIII", "George I", "George II"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What musical instrument did action star Steven Seagal learn to play, and later used as an accompaniment to his vocal performances?", "correct_answer": "Guitar", "incorrect_answers": ["Banjo", "Piano", "Saxophone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Youre one sad strange little man is a line from this movie.", "correct_answer": "Toy Story", "incorrect_answers": ["Ratatoiullie", "A Bugs Life", "The Incredibles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Finish the title of a song from the Hit TV Series, The Drew Carey Show.\nMoon Over ____", "correct_answer": "Parma", "incorrect_answers": ["Pittsburgh", "Shaker Heights", "Miamisburg"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which European city is the headquarters of Interpol located?", "correct_answer": "Lyon", "incorrect_answers": ["Geneva", "London", "Paris"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not a part of the badgers diet?", "correct_answer": "Insects", "incorrect_answers": ["Birds", "Ground squirrels", "Rattlesnakes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these foods does the Canada goose include in its diet?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Green vegetation", "Grains", "Seaweeds"]}]